<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Factorization Mod for Minecraft</string>
    <string name="title">Factorization Mod</string>
    <string name="mod_file">FactorizationLauncher v1.0.js</string>
    <string name="texture_pack_file">Resources - factorization 4.7.3.zip</string>
    <string name="additional_file">FactorizationSound.zip</string>
    <string name="appodeal_id">5bbcbac4583885c52b31c66b71a443dd83c335f1d3de4efc</string>

    <string name="main_text">    This mod completely changes the game experience. It have everything from famous mods like Industrial craft 2, buildcraft, forestry and greg tech from PC version of the game. This mod is extremely big.\n\n
             Mod includes:\n
            1. about 45 mechanisms and more objects.\n
            2. 5 new ore generation gevey and lakes of oil.\n
            3. Wires and elaboration of energy, both in the industrial craft 2, generators and nuclear reactor.\n
            4. Pipes are very similar to pipes BuildCraft\n
            5. User-friendly and beautiful interface for most mechanisms\n
            6. Working fluids, of which 6 - new, in particular oil, which flows like water, capsules\n
            7. Beekeeping!\n
            8. Auto-farm animals and plants\n
            9. Automatic extraction of ore\n
            10. 2 types of rechargeable new armor.\n
            11. New ways of processing resources\n
            12. Weapons and tools, working on energy.\n
            13. The ability to create add-ons to the basic mode.\n
            14. Good graphics and a beautiful model of some blocks.\n
            15. The file for advanced settings\n
            16. The new structure is generated in the world\n
            \n
            With blocks, mechanisms based on which events, you can create huge systems that produce, process and provide any resources!\n
            \n
            As mentioned earlier, the survival of the mod is quite real. You gather resources, and create a simple generators, handlers and tools. With them you can get resources faster and in greater numbers. Then you can go on any of the many paths of development - from the creation of matter and quantum, to the peace of beekeeping and automatic farming. What to do - you decide!
    </string>
</resources>
