<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Morph Mod for Minecraft</string>
    <string name="title">Morph Mod</string>
    <string name="mod_file">MorphMod.js</string>

    <string name="appodeal_id">567a8a23d11b3782952e4f890e398858b0f9124690f8e529</string>

    <string name="main_text">
        Morph Mod will allow you to transform into any monsters and animals that exist in the world of Minecraft Pocket Edition. The main feature is that this mod not only changes your skin at the selected animal or creature, but it gives you the properties of the selected creature. For example, if you turn into a creeper, you can explode, turning into a bat gives you ability to fly and see at night, turning into a spider, ability to climb the wall.\n
         \n
        Morph is really cool modification for Minecraft Pocket Edition. With it, you can feel in the \"skin\" of each creature, and to be understand how it to be as a cow, wolf or skeleton, which can be located on the surface only during the day!\n
        \n
        How to use?\n
        \n
        When you enter the world of MCPE, in the lower right corner of the screen you will see a button \"M\" - click on it and you will open the menu of transformations!\n
        \n
        To turn into someone simply click on the icon of the creature you want to turn in. For example, we want to turn into a mushroom cow - we click on that icon and turning into a sweet cow.\n
        \n
        You can also turn into a bat and have all the benefits that bats have. You can fly through a small slit where the original character cant. The ability to quickly move through the air gives you many benefits, but the most important thing is that the bat has the ability to see at night!\n
        \n
        When you will become a creeper you will also have the most amazing opportunity to explode, but you can do it at any time by pressing the button \"B\".\n
        \n
        If you turn into a snowman, you will be able to leave the snow behind.\n
        \n
        With Morph mod you can turn into any other animals and monsters that exist in the amazing world of Minecraft: Pocket Edition.\n
    </string>
</resources>


